(Leonard:)I figured it would go for thousands,
and I just wanted to be a part of it.
- There's only 30 seconds left in the auction.
- Do you have $800?
- Not to blow on a miniature time machine.
- Don't worry.
People wait until the last second,
then they get it. It's called sniping.
- Fifteen seconds.
- Come on, snipers.
- Ten, nine, eight...
- Where are your snipers?
- Five.
- Snipe.
(Howard:)- Four.
- Three, two.
- Snipe, snipe.
(Raj:)- One.
- Ah!
Oh. Congratulations, you are the proud
owner of a miniature time machine.
- You lucky duck.
LEONARD: Heh.
I wonder why no one else bid.
(Sheldon:)This is a classic piece
of sci-fi movie memorabilia.
I know. But I still can't afford it.
(Howard:)Why don't we share it?
We'll each put in 200 bucks...
- ...and take turns having it in our house.
- A time-share time machine.
(Raj:)- I'm in. Sheldon?
- Wha...? Need you ask?
(Sheldon:)But I still don't understand
why no one else bid.
I understand why no one else bid.